{
    "subject": "resource/Bj\u00f6rn_Westerlund",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathYear",
    "object": "2009",
    "human_readable": "Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund died in 2009.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8801683187484741,
            "question": "When did Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7517017126083374,
            "question": "Is Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund still alive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6449316740036011,
            "question": "Where was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6311602592468262,
            "question": "In what year was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5003808736801147,
            "question": "What year marked the passing of Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.442333459854126,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43395891785621643,
            "question": "Was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund known for any particular achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4243728220462799,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4161812365055084,
            "question": "What was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's impact on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.408239483833313,
            "question": "What was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund died in 2009.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2218_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's impact on the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2218_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events associated with Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2218_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund known for any particular achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2218_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2218_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention that Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund died in 2009. In fact, they provide information about him being alive, with references to his Instagram account and Facebook page."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThe documents do not contain any information about Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's date of death. They provide details about his profession, interests, and personality type but do not mention anything regarding his death in 2009. Therefore, the given statement is unsupported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund, as described in the context information, is an artist, educator, and person living currently in Sandarna. Therefore, he has not died in 2009.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Context information describes Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund as an active artist and educator, with social media presence. This indicates he is still alive.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "I don't have enough information to conclude that the statement \"Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund died in 2009\" is wrong, but based on the available context, I can make an educated guess:\n\n There's no mention of Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund dying in 2009 anywhere in the provided context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Bj\u00f6rn Westerlund's death. Additionally, the information available describes him as an artist, educator, and current presence on social media platforms like Instagram and Facebook, indicating he is still active.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}